在Forecast Fragment类里，
In the Forecast Fragment class, we add the callback
我们添加一个要点里列出的回调函数。然后在onCreateView的方法中
that was provided in the gist. Then in the onCreateView
我们修改表项被点击的操作。 当一个项目被
method, we modify the item click behavior. When an
点击之后，将Cursor移动至那个所点击 的位置，
item is clicked, we move the cursor to that position
来读取字符串数据。我们
and then we read out the date string. We
调用getActivity方法，并且把它类型转换为Callback对象
call getActivity and then we cast it to a Callback
然后我们调用onItemSelected方法，并将日期字符作为参数传递。
object. And then we call onItemSelected, with that date
然后在MainActivity中，我们实现回调函数的代码。
string. Then in the MainActivity, we implement this Callback interface.
在onItemSelected方法中，
In the onItemSelected method, we fork behavior based on
我们根据之前定义的TwoPane的值来决定接下来的操作。如果我们是在双
the TwoPane variable that we defined earlier. If we're
面板状态中，我们需要创建一个新的DetailFragment
in TwoPane mode, then we create a new DetailFragment
来使用arguments bundle的日 期数据。 然后我们
using the date in the arguments bundle. And then
用weather_detail_container替换已经有的fragment。不过，
we replace the existing fragment in the weather_detail_container. Otherwise,
在单面板状态中，我们需要创建一个新的意向来
in OnePane mode, we create a new intent to
启动detail activity，并把日期数据放到Intent Extra里
launch the detail activity setting the date as an
。在detail activity里，需要修改一下onCreate方法，
intent extra. In the detail activity, we modify the onCreate
目的是来读取从main activity传入的intent数据
method to read the intent extras from the intent that
我们把这些日期数据放入bundle中，
came from the main activity. We take this date and set
用这个bundle来初始化detail fragment
it in the arguments bundle to initialize the detail fragment.
同时将detail fragment动态的加入进这个容器内。在
And we dynamically add the detail fragment to this container. In
detail fragment中，修改onCreateLoader方法
the detail fragment, we modify the on create loader method
来读取那些传入的参数。我们使用
to read from the arguments that were passed in. We get
日期的字符串并且用它
the date string out and use it with the location
和地点字符串一起组成一个URI来请求Content provider。
string to build up the Uri to query the content provider.
我们还需要移除一些对于传入Intent的依赖。
We also remove any reliance on the incoming intent.
使用一个arguments bundle来替代它。举个例子
We switch it to use the arguments bundle, instead. For
在onActivityCreated方法中，只有在参数不为空时
example, in the onActivityCreated method, we only initialize the loader
我们才会初始化loader。在 onResume 方法中，
if the arguments is not null. In the onResume method,
我们也需要修改一些条件，这样程序会检查这个
we also modify the condition so that it checks that
bundle是不是空。 当你在平板上
the arguments bundle is not null. When you try it
测试的时候，会出现一个页面导航相关的bug
out on the tablet, there is one bug related to
比如我们选择了未来的日期
navigation that we should fix. Say we select tomorrows date.
如果你转向设置页面
If you navigate to the settings activity and then hit
然后点击向上的按键，detail fragment就变成空白的。 这是因为
the up button, the detail fragment is blank. That's because
系统重新实例化了一个main activity
a brand new instance of main activity got launched and
而在新的实例中，我们什么都没选择。
for a brand new instance, nothing is selected yet. To fix
要解决这个bug，在设置页面的上键被按下之后，
this, when the settings activity up button is pressed, we
必须要把之前运行的main activity实例找出来
want to navigate to the previous running instance of the
找出来，而且这时选择了未来的事件。而不去
main activity, where the tomorrow item is selected. And not
创建一个新的main activity实例。 在设置页面里，
create a new instance of main activity. In the settings activity,
重写这个方法。系统通过调用这个方法，
overwrite this method. Which the system will call in
来获得上一级activity的intent来响应上按键的操作。
order to get the parent activity intent for the up
当我们拿到父activiyt的Intent后
button behaviour. Get the parent activity intent from the
它会在main activity中创建一个新的
super class, this should create a new intent to main
Intent。然后加入一个意向标志，叫做 FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_TOP。
activity. Then add the intent flag, called FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_TOP. This
这个标志会告诉我们main activity是否已经在我们
flag indicates that we should check if the main activity
的任务中运行。我们要使用这个
is already running in our task. And to use
标志，来避免必须要创建一个新的活动实例外。
that one, instead of creating a new main activity instance.
同时这个方法不能在Jelly Bean之前安卓系统上使用。所以我们
Also, this method didn't exist prior to jelly bean, so we need
需要在目标API里加入这个声明。所以如果你已经查找了一些关于
to add this at target API annotation. If you check the documentation
activity类的文档，getParentActivityIntent 方法仅有在API 16级之后才被加入。
for the activity class, the getParentActivityIntent method was only added in API
你可以在16版本中的找到该方法。
level 16. And you can check that version 16 maps to jelly bean.